YEP
THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENS.
YOU GO
TO WAR
WITH ONE
OF THESE
BREAKFAST BURRITOS.
AS I
WAS SAYING
BEFORE
ALBERTO'S IS
ONE OF
THE BEST
IN SAN
DIEGO.
KNOWN FOR
ITS TREMENDOUS
GUAC.
PULLING UP
TO ALBERTO'S.
THIS IS
THE OG.
YEAH
CAN I
GET A
BREAKFAST BURRITO
WITH
UH
HAM
EGG
AND GUACAMOLE
AND CHEESE
PLEASE?
THAT'S GOOD.
IT IS
$15.42.
IN LINE
LET'S GET
SOMETHING STRAIGHT.
WE ARE
NOT GONNA
PUT POTATOES
IN MY
BREAKFAST BURRITO.
IT'S SORT
OF LIKE
P- UH
PINEAPPLE ON
A PIZZA.
WE JUST
DON'T DO
IT.
IT'S NOT
GOOD.
NO ONE
ASKS FOR
IT.
LET'S NOT
GO THERE.
GOT THAT
ICONIC DRIVE
AROUND
ALMOST WIENER
SCHNITZEL LOOKING
BUILDING.
NEVER BEEN
CLEANED
PROBABLY THIRTY
YEARS.
BUT THEY
GOT THAT
A RATING
THANK GOD.
AND THEN
OF COURSE
THIS IS
ALWAYS THE
UH
FUN PART
OF EATING
HERE.
ONE IS
THE PARKING
LOT SUCKS
THIS GUY
WANTS TO
GET OUT.
THERE'S NOWHERE
TO GO.
YEAH
THERE'S NOWHERE
FOR HIM
TO GO.
HE'S SCREWED.
HERE WE
GO.
HERE'S THE
UNVEILING.
OH
YEAH.
YOU SEE
ALL THAT
GREEN IN
THERE?
THAT IS
ALL FRESH
GUACAMOLE.
UNBELIEVABLE.
OH
SNAP.
HOLY S***
THAT IS
GOOD.
SO ONE
THING I
LIKE ABOUT
IT
IT'S THE
RIGHT AMOUNT
OF CHEESE.
THE GUAC
IS TREMENDOUS.
THIS IS
A HAM
AND EGG.
THIS THING'S
PISSING ALL
OVER ME
BUT THAT'S
THE SIGN
OF A
GOOD MEXICAN
BREAKFAST BURRITO.
SO MUCH
JUICE IN
THIS THING
FROM THE
EGGS TO
HAM
CHEESE.
DRIVE-THROUGH WITH
THE
UH
MICROPHONE THAT
YOU BASICALLY
CAN'T HEAR
S*** OUT
OF.
SOUNDS LIKE
A SQUAWK
BOX.
WHO KNOWS
WHAT THEY'RE
SAYING.
WHO KNOWS
IF YOU'RE
GONNA GET
YOUR ORDER
BUT YOU
WOULDN'T WANT
IT ANY
OTHER WAY.
THEY'RE LITERALLY
RIGHT NEXT
TO A
TACO BELL.
I MEAN
WHO WOULD
GO TO
A FREAKING
TACO BELL
AND GET
THE DIARRHEA
SALAD LETTUCE
THAT THEY'RE
PUTTING ON
THAT S***
WHEN YOU
COULD BE
SITTING RIGHT
HERE AT
EL ALBERTO'S?
AGAIN
I THINK
UH
I'M GONNA
HAVE TO
GIVE THIS
A SCORE
OF I'M
GONNA GO
FOUR TAPATIOS.
I WAS
GONNA GO
THREE AND
A HALF
BASED ON
THE CLEANLINESS
OF THE
PLACE
A LITTLE
SKETCHY
BUT THE
FOOD IS
TOO FREAKING
GOOD.
SO AMIGOS
IT'S GONNA
GET FOUR
TAPATIOS.
THAT'S ALMOST
ONE OF
OUR HIGHEST
AWARDS
FOR THE
BREAKFAST BURRITO
REVIEW.
ALL RIGHT
SIGNING OFF
MR.
TACO SHOP.
LET'S GO
SI SE
PUEDE.